

### Summary

Designer with experience in social media design and a passion for telling stories. Whether it be in captions in social media, in front of large crowds, or behind the scenes in a video. I am an expert in helping you get your ideas out there.

#### Contact

PHONE:

210-379-0209

**EMAIL:** 

aa.camp.ron.bell@gmail.com

LINKED IN URL:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaron-campbell-870a7576/

# Aaron Campbell

SOCIAL MEDIA DESIGNER

#### **EDUCATION**

Texas A&M San Antonio – Communications – Journalism May 2016 – May 2020[

San Antonio College – Speech Communication August 2012 – May 2015

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

HCL- USAA - Service Desk - IT June 2021-Present

Worked with customers to find and troubleshoot computer issues.

#### Success Engine – CRM Couch January 2021–May 2021

Assessed, designed, developed, and delivered training solutions at all levels of staff for multiple and multiple business functions including inside, outside and independent sales force, internal support groups and external clients.

#### Urban Bricks Pizza - Social Media Intern November 2019–March 2020

Managed content, developed media plans and updated social media, including Facebook, Instagram and Twitter, with a focus on increasing awareness and engagement.

Develop and schedule weekly social media messages. Coordinated the development of pitch stories and messaging.

#### Little Authors – Publishing Assistant October 2020- June 2021

Edited books from start to finish for proper grammar and clarity.

Produced and assembled graphics for children's stories.

Communicated with adults and children on clarity and structure of narrative for publishing.

Managed brick and mortar storefront, and social media accounts

## **SKILLS**

Bilingual in Spanish

Experience in Video and Audio production

Literate in Microsoft Office and Adobe Creative Suite

Ability to understand and deliver information verbally in front of large groups.

Experience in social media, and web content production.